livesimply.me 2017-10-01

# Disclosure Policy - Live Simply

This policy is valid from 12 February 2016.

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by Kristin Marr. For questions about this blog, please contact me.

This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this blog is not compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the blog owners. If we claim or appear to be experts on a certain topic or product or service area, we will only endorse products or services that we believe, based on our expertise, are worthy of such endorsement. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer or provider.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

Privacy Policy for www.livesimply.me

At www.livesimply.me, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy outlines the type of personal information that is received and collected by www.livesimply.me and how it is used.

## LOG FILES

Like many other Web sites, www.livesimply.me makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS

Cookies are very small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit some websites. Cookies are used by most websites to tailor content and marketing messages to better suit your needs.

We use cookies on the website to track visitor behavior. If you prefer not to allow the use of cookies, you can change the configuration of your browser to warn you when you receive a cookie or automatically reject them.

If you would like to find out more about cookies you can visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

### TYPES OF COOKIE USED

**Google Analytics** – We use Google Analytics to understand how the website is being used in order to improve the user experience. User data is anonymous.

**Google Remarketing** — Google uses these cookies to show relevant adverts to users who have previously visited our website, as they browse other websites. You can opt-out from Google’s remarketing program, by changing your Google Ad Settings.

**Facebook** – Cookies and pixels are used to understand and deliver ads and make them more relevant to you. We may also use a cookie to learn whether someone who saw an ad on Facebook later visited our website.

## DOUBLECLICK DART COOKIE

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.livesimply.me.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.livesimply.me and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include…

Google Adsense  
Sovrn  
Yellow Hammer Media  
Amazon  
ADThrive

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.livesimply.me send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.livesimply.me uses Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using Google’s [Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) page. Users can completely block Google Analytics tracking using [Google’s Analytics Opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.livesimply.me’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

If you make this recipe, be sure to snap a photo and hashtag it [#LIVESIMPLYBLOG](https://www.instagram.com/explore/tags/livesimplyblog/). I'd love to see what you make!
